My face we borrowed a stranger
Every whisper found a hungry crowd
Every spark became a flame
They say they know what's in my heart
Like they live beneath my skin
But no one sees the steepest nights
I'm sorry, I don't have anything to say about these people there are the witches are the fuck are they demons
You remember demons?
Christine six six six six six six
Beat is kiddies BKG all is under mayors IRL news time and IP to wiki info demons
They are fucking demons out prove me prove me wrong. These are these are demons. These are demonic entities
they're not human beings human beings have a heart human beings have a soul these are soulless
witches these are people that are they're demonically possessed this is purely me this is purely me
yo let's get into it why can't i be a movie star i will be a movie star i'll be a fucking movie
star okay i'm gonna write a movie out of this fucking shit that is my life right now because of
Look at these people. Are these real people? Look at these people. Look how ugly they are.
Look how ugly they fucking are. This is what they look like, okay?
This doesn't make me make you shit up. This is how ugly they are. They're fucking disgusting ugly demons.
Prove me wrong. Oh, hold on one second. Not that. Look, here. These are the demons.
Look at these people. Look at how disgusting they are.
The fat person fucking whore!
Fucking black ain't ridden bitch fucking fat Puerto Rican piece of slime
sick
You're sick people
I'm gonna say I'm messed up. Look at these. Look at them. They're disgusting. Can you see the demonic entities on there?
Like it upset. These are demonic entities, okay? I'm looking about and they're like it's just as right up
These are fucking demonic
Disgusting the most disgusting people I've ever met in my life
I was on her mayor's kicked out of the adult entertainment industry because if you had green she come out of a vagina
Now I'm having a
Delicious meal, right? I'm gonna I'm gonna write the movie though. I'm gonna write. I don't have to say any more
They're demons
The only one with any good looks is but she doesn't really have good looks
They're demons these people accusing me of animal abuse every day
They're people that are putting my mom's name out there.
They're people that are making memes out of my dead father
and then they're crying about their father
that I'd never mess with.
I'd never mess with your father.
Did I?
They're sick.
They're sick fucking people.
What are you doing so go into their channels?
What the fuck are you thinking?
They're the demons.
They're these Hollywood special effects on these people.
They're ugly demons.
Let me see Alexander Mayer's the white version. I'll show you the white version of her. Okay.
Watch this. Watch this. Hey, great bull. I can't wait to take this anymore. It's like so, so sick.
These two are so sick. Watch this. The white Alexander Mayer's. Watch this. Tell me this is not her.
Tell me this is not her. Do anything to be famous.
to be on television you're not anybody in america unless you're on tv was a chance
she would die for good evening wwe and weathers weathers actually ever been on television
before to be a star you've got to be able to do things that ordinary people wouldn't do was the
I don't think I need to tell you that today was a hard day.
Hey, yeah, what's going on?
What are you yelling?
I annexed, Pina says today, I abused my cats.
She says, you know, she branched my cats by name,
saying I'm a cat abuser, animal abuser.
Her mods call me animal abuser, hide me out of her chat.
All that's under mayor says I'm giving her death threats,
when she's giving me death threats.
Sam has called me an animal abuser and cat abuser.
You know, this hurts my heart.
I'm the opposite of those things.
I understand.
I get it.
I know I love animals, too.
It is hurtful to hear that, but you know it's not true,
and people around you know it's not true.
I know, but a lot of people believe it.
A lot of people believe it.
Yeah, you need to see that.
That's a good move.
Those are people that don't matter,
and a friend of mine just reminded me earlier
when I got on a panel.
And she called me and it's one of the people that Crystal keeps mentioning that's been done with her because she she doesn't do this drama anymore after Astro mom or whatever.
I was going to strike me today and beat us right in the strike me about 10 times.
Who's got you?
I was Sandra.
Where?
On my on this channel she shook off from the first channel and you know what it's for it's for a video
That has my mother's name on the title of it and my full legal name on the title of it and she's striking me for it
I did a privacy complaint right back, right?
But this sick bitch. I mean, this is a sick bitch. What's wrong with this person? What is fucking wrong with this woman?
You're upset I know you know anything to her I never did one thing to her
What did I never knew to her just ready to kill me to Christina's agree with it be this can be ever chat
But Venus a piece of shit and like Barb said she she lies, but then Barb is pretty messy herself
I don't like Barb, you know
But I just wait bonding because you look at my videos on her bashing crystal and calling her nuts
I have three videos. She just hate bonding and needs your attention
And she won't show her recent picture or anything.
She's shown an old cartoon image of a picture of her.
I saw what she looks like.
I'm sorry I'm getting upset, but it's like, I can only be pushed so far.
I can only be pushed called an animal because there's so many times.
I can only be said I'm some fucking loser that doesn't know anything.
I take advantage of women. I'm an extorter, blackmailer.
I can only be called these so many times before I react.
And then they're sitting there, she's just laughing along with Bita.
Not like she didn't slander Bita for the last year, using her last name,
saying her family owned slaves in Iran.
Oh, but Bita's clean. But Bita's clean, right?
You know, it's not clean. She's missing. She's a liar. And Barb did lie about the 5150 because those two ex-friends have been pissed off and said she's a liar.
And they gave Barb money because she was staying at her sister's couch. Her husband left her. This is during COVID. I don't know about now, but she was staying on her sister's couch and she hardly had any money.
And all of them, including Jamie, would loan us a few dollars through cash up so she could go get Ben and Jerry's ice cream because she used to walk to the store that was nearby her sister's place.
And.
And then it build up like she owed them 60 70 $80, but she'd pay it back with a little interest
And Nancy said the same thing and I heard me to say the exact same thing
She gave her money so she doesn't know her she's a no barb $300. Well as for me
They're telling people not to donate to me, you know after all this slander and everything when people don't even want to donate to me
They're telling people not to donate to me these sick fucks. They're sick
Me they're calling me sick and just don't go to their panels
You get a good following on your channels
But the people listen to her let people listen to them and it's like and then they come in here bother me
Saman comes up saying I'm a cat I like him. He's everywhere and I'm glad how cake a cake I called him out
You know, he's embarrassed. He won't show face. He's fat. Yeah, he looks awful now and the only person he
Face times with this is beta who won't show her real face. I mean come on
I mean you saw her real picture and Q knows it because he saw her face and I have more pictures of her
She has skin tags around her eyes on the top and below and see that's why she won't show her face
Do you see the picture on the screen? I mean, this is what we have with here
This isn't the new best friends of the community right there
That will last long because it is nuts. Magman fucking
Yeah look at him man he won't show face at all. Disgusting. I mean they're fucking disgust and I'm
sorry I'm overreacting or I'm getting emotional about it. I just can't take it anymore. It is
continually, continually, I mean I don't even, I'm even defending her about the cat's whiskers
today and shit like that. I keep trying to defend her. I mean they're taking business away from me,
they're getting people away from me, they're saying I'm the piece of shit. When they're
I don't know why you got on crystals crystal is crazy and I just reminded her and I showed her communication we used to have and I said what happened to that crystal that's a crystal I thought I was getting to know and miss I said ever since you came on panels or or joined you to begin your your monster
Let her show that yeah, maybe she should show what I said her and that was her communication before she you know
All this took over. It's like she's a different person. She's evil
She's become a bully and that's not the crystal I was talking to when she reached out to me when I was sick
And even Allison bitch today. She said well be that asked me
You know for my address so I get so she can send me jewelry just like be that asked me for my address
So she can send me some cat toys. Do you know what I never received a cat toys?
But my address, my address is good at Eldo though. My address is good at Eldo.
But no, yeah, no cat toys, we had my old address and she sent me it was some yeah, it was my birthday and her and Karen hold on. I'm psyche psyche. I always came back to the community to call clumsy what he was doing beyond the scenes.
Okay. And then I came out the other night and I was talking on your panel with with Karen.
Okay, but the whole like let's just leave all that shit, you know all that
Karen and psyche, I'm not working with be a beyond the scenes. Please don't say that
I know I don't talk with any people behind the scenes
If I did where's the screenshots where's the proof I don't talk with any people behind the scenes, okay?
Yeah, but why'd you ask I'm grateful to get off of YouTube and you made a blood pack or something with that
Then you were there whoa, whoa, don't guess I be I just say
You were there the next day. You said we both
I didn't I just say blood packed
Your parents you swore on your parents that you wouldn't be back on YouTube and you were
there the next day, but I saw her there.
That's why I said.
Oh, that's why you had to be on YouTube to see me and I was just posting something on
my YouTube.
And yes, and that was that was my main account.
I'm not on all.
I don't use.
Okay.
Just a main account wasn't supposed to go on YouTube again.
Architect.
Yeah.
That's my main account outside of this community.
outside this community, right?
Yeah, guys, look up Jimmy Death.
Jimmy, J-I-M-M-Y, underscore death.
That's Rob666 in the chat.
People think that YouTube is just
this community right here.
YouTube is like more bigger than this.
I didn't know about this community,
this topic community,
because I've had YouTube since 2014.
It was just for music and they had the DMs
and we DMed our friends, people I knew.
And then all of a sudden, it was Gia that pulled me into this because she wanted me to defend her to a guy called Ganville, who was calling her parents with the guy named, what was his name, that other guy, his friend.
Gamble and Vern, and they mobbed her through Craig List, and she got in trouble with her
family and a rookie Reina was reached, it was really bad, so she was scared, and she
brought me on to see these people, I said what is that, well now hang on, and she said
it's a panel, that's Gamble, she said he's gonna call my parents again, he's been calling
comes on and she's sending me a text with the phone number and I said is that that guy Gamble's number and she said yes
So, you know, Jill was crying because she was scared because they mobbed her and
This is how the first time I knew of this so when I called that number
I was expecting a guy to answer and I heard a lot of noise and he was being a jerk
and there was a lot of background noise and I asked Gia said what what's that noise in the
background no listen listen listen I said what's that noise in the background and she said he's
live and I said what what do you mean live I thought it was calling a guy on his regular phone to
tell him hey stop harassing or calling her family I didn't know about lives until that was my first
Okay, fantastic. Okay, listen, when I responded, when I replied to you as I thought we're making
impact, that was all, I don't run all, I run accounts, okay?
No, no, okay, yeah.
I don't do this all shit, and I'm not working with B2B on the scenes, okay?
I was just getting off of YouTube though. Why are you so interested? You were very invested
that night, right?
Because, because, because I think she's so invested.
No, not really. I was like, like, like, I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like,
I
Let it get me triggered. Yeah, so I'm being more careful now Carl, you know, and I'm
I'm invested look at I haven't been on I'm not going live on my own channel because I don't have that anymore
But look at watch you anyway watch you in a carl no one cares
But listen to what she was saying right now. I think she's invested in five years ago Karen chill out chill out
You gotta chill out. I'm not hopping all these panels. I get on psyches and that's it right now
I don't get on all these boys. You do your own stuff though, too. I mean, this is all new
Hey, this is for your well-being. Yeah, you know, I know I'm being careful because you know what Carl?
I started getting really upset earlier when I came home
I started making a video to go at some asshole because I
He has no, listen, you can, you can, you can, you can literally, you can literally turn.
No, I'm trying to explain something. So yeah, he needs to get off. I don't want him on there.
I'm not going to be interrupted like that. I'm not Mimi. Okay.
But yeah, so that's, that's what happened. But you know what? Today I started getting triggered
and a friend called me and knew it. And so we talked and I said, you know what? I can't watch
And now they're going at each other
Yeah, so that's it but that calmed me down and so I got off for a while and I've been
We I went out there to feed the feral's with a friend of mine and yeah
And now I'm over here tending to my babies
They're getting along and I'm happy the bully cat. She's been chilled with the baby cat
Oh see and the baby looks like like your cat
I miss kitty so much, you know, and so I was thinking of naming her kitty the new little kitten
Yeah, but my friend Jamie said no don't do that, you know, because you know that was a special cat and I said, yeah
And she said call her Annabelle
You think that'll be a cute name for this baby
We ever saw the movie with Annabelle?
Is that doll that's that scary doll, right? Oh my god. I think I'm gonna stick with kid. I don't know kitty was special
Kitty I like baby. I like I like those kind of names, you know Annabelle's a little bit
You know animals a little bit evil, and I know I don't need an evil cat or something
Which is adorable and she sticks with me and yesterday had a scare. I had to take boxes out the throw out.
I open the door and then they kind of come out with me and then I thought, oh my God, she might run off like they said, you know, nine other people try to take her home and then she ran ran away and ended up by the front of the office.
And she was gone, I thought.
And I thought, oh, shit, man, I said,
and I went ahead and threw the boxes away.
And then I came back looking for her.
And no, she was there waiting for me in the corner,
like, hey, mommy, and I picked her up.
No problem, brought her in.
And she's just happy inside.
And she just loves to curl up with me wherever I go.
She wants me to carry her.
Right.
I mean, cats are, you know,
They're very sweet animals, and we love cats, and I know you do, and it's like...
I do now. I've been a dog person.
Yeah, and my pecanese is chilled with them and another lady that has the pecanese on Instagram
You know there my our pecanese's are always show quality
She has a beautiful show quality pecanese and we started talking because she asked me she goes
How do you get your your cats to get along with your pecanese? She goes?
I've had pecanese's and and my cat and the pecanese don't get along
I said, I don't know. I just treat them the same pretty much. I don't try to separate
them. She goes, oh, no wonder. I said, yeah. She goes, I love the picture, how they chill
together and sleeping together, especially the picture of my Pekingese sitting and looking
out the window looking at me and the cats around them. It's just so cute.
But I don't know where she's at.
I like the fake grass that she has on her patio.
Yeah, well, when I got off my last show,
I started getting phone calls.
And this was.
Let me see. Hold on one second. I'm getting a message from my friend. Oh, you know what?
This is a sign. This is a sign. My friend, I have a Russian friend, okay?
And guess what? She just texted me and guess what is in the text?
Look at the names of her cats, her favorite cats.
Elvira and Annabelle. Oh, Annabelle. Look at Annabelle.
Yeah, and juror. Okay, so Rob. Okay, this is either like big tall sexy Rob probably but it's also probably Tony
I was getting these phone calls today saying I'm a PDF
You know leave leave beta alone and also here. I was getting phone. I'll show you the phone call log
Look at look at this. So this is a phone calls. These are all the phone calls that all I'm trying to call me
Today, let me see. It's just okay. One two three four five six eight one number of West Virginia
If anyone knows
Virginia yeah, Rob go away beat all sexy Rob. Get the fuck out of here bitch. You're not welcome here
I'm gonna get a bit of a cow you fucking you you stupid mother
He's a six foot tall six foot seven Samoan that it was a Chippendales
I saw his pictures. He's a bald fat ugly fucker. He's
Rasting me. Are you're inviting the answer and he's yeah
It was more like Chip and Dale's dancer. It was a dancer for Chipmunks. That's the only people that find him attractive. He's wrote it. Out!
Yeah, damn, man. Yeah, I don't know. It's just gone crazy, though, you know. It's hard to trust anybody online. It's different than the people that we know in our real lives.
Right. And I'm just going to get the number of this person who harassed me. I'm going to get their phone number out because they're just going too far.
No, don't get it. Don't give it out online because it gets crazy because remember Crystal had given my number out and then I had that guy Bruno that was threatening to kill me and my pets caused twice.
681, 680, 6169. There you go. Sorry, baby. No, he's just calling me harassing me. It's just praying calling.
Oh, he is?
Yeah, yeah. It's not even.
No, damn.
Yeah, I gave his phone number. It's probably just a text now number, but go ahead and call him and and ask him
It's not going to call him. I've got my baby over here cuddled up. Yeah, the chat the chat. I'm not you
Nancy are you gonna call him reality Nancy?
Oh, there he is. He's coming back. Oh Rob. We know big-tall sexy Rob. You you fucking little midget
Samoan he's the ugliest fucker. I'm gonna I'm gonna go back to JT. JT has a picture
I'm gonna post this picture everywhere. Why is he calling you? What happened? He's mad
Yeah, he's mad, but I'm gonna say I'm gonna add his picture to that one.
Oh, here he is, and now I'm gonna text messages from it.
Well, he's not in the picture, is he?
He's not...
Well, not yet. I mean, he's uglier than Samman.
He's even uglier than Samman, if you remember.
Samman.
But he says, right now, he says, he says, and he says,
he says, get a job, get a job, get a job, get a job.
You can see right here, he texted me that.
Get a job, get a job, get a job, get a job.
I have a job.
Oh, my God, he's blowing you up.
I didn't block him.
You can't block him.
Yeah, I'm going to block him right now.
I'm going to block it.
I think he just posted many mansons of vagina.
And so I'm going to restart the stream because I don't love that many
mansons of vagina was seen on the stream.
Oh, shit.
We started just, you know, keep on.
I wouldn't get to you like that, psyche.
And just, yeah.
I know, I just want to make sure that you can see many Mansons vagina because yeah
I don't like the way crystal all of a sudden she's acting like she's supporting Rick when she said she was done with them
Because in April of 2021 they were gonna do a live on her and all of a sudden this woman Ella showed up
I don't know what happened and started attacking her instead
And that's how she came around, but yeah, they did called to do a, well, I was going to say reality check, you know, when they called the mental place on her, they were all involved in that. I remember that.
Please don't do that to these people. These people are insane.
They are nuts.
Oh, here he goes again.
What does he say?
Get a job.
How about you get a job?
I have a job.
I'm actually in a nice apartment by the ocean.
I'm very secure, very safe.
I have enough money for food.
I'm doing good.
But you need to get a job, I think, because you're sitting on YouTube of sexy Rob harassing
somebody.
That's all you can do.
How many accounts do you have, sexy Rob?
Yeah man, I don't know if your name is Rob. You're disgusting. Oh, look, I lose. Okay, well, you know,
you lose because you're just gonna keep getting hit and then you have less and less accounts to
do it on. Oh, you're such a bitch. You're such a bitch, N-word. I mean-
Would y'all used to be cool before and he just started-
No, he just comes in harassing me. He just comes in harassing me under different alts and stuff
like that. I think he's, I'm toting the, I mean, I talked to him tonight. He's like, oh, oh, oh, here,
Uh, Rob always wins. Oh, you're a PDF.
The term for Rob always wins.
Yeah, Big Rob, Big Rob, your little Rob, you have an employee in complex because there's such a little bitch n-word, okay?
Little Rob666, who's also Jimmy Death on Kiwi Farms. Look up Jimmy Death, J-M-Y Death on Kiwi Farms, probably friends with Black RG.
Look up on Kiwi Farms, look up the Kennel Kickers on Kiwi Farms, and look up, um, Elzunder Mayers on Kiwi Farms.
You can find out the truth about all these disgusting demons! They're demons!
They're dangerous because remember that lady I told you about royal black was her name and she was pretty well known from the
Cardiverse and
Erin would have her on his live on YouTube and she wouldn't show face
But I remember he was playing games sometimes and he was pretending that she was his private investigator
I think against Crystal and some other people.
I recognized her voice because we were cool and she was on my IG.
She was a tough one.
That was somebody you didn't fuck with because she,
I mean, especially with Crystal,
she used to let her have it.
But then one time she got nervous because they found her.
Kiwi did and I didn't know who they were and she goes,
you don't know who Kiwi farms is?
I said, no, she goes, it's a bad, bad group of people.
and she was scared because they found her on my IG and I didn't know who they were.
You know what's good about them is that they don't like these other doctors that are doing real
life and sending you know the concrete and sending the doorknob people's houses because
they're like oh these people are these moral they're these moral big fake moral people that
call anybody if you're 25 if you're 25 year old woman
They have a 35 year old guy talking to you.
They call that guy a PDF because, you know, he's, he's 20,
they call like a 25 year old woman a kid now, right?
Right?
Isn't that great?
Right, yeah.
Yeah.
You know what?
I'm very healthy and you've seen me.
I'm very healthy and I'm glad I'm happy.
Right, so now I got these babies and we had bad weather all week long
It finally today was a great day, but it started raining tonight for a little bit
Shan tell him to stop that because he's calling my she's calling me and he's harassing me
Shan if you know this guy tell him to stop, please
We're ten accounts in this one chat
Like Brandon does that. He has a million accounts.
I want to clear it up guys that Alex never sent him money.
He made it a fake don't know thing.
I didn't know because I remember.
A gamble said that he made fake accounts and I didn't know notice he made a lot even to join your panel remember and making crazy faces and going nuts on you.
He called me, he called me several times today and I talked to on the phone. So yes, it is him the same person. Yes.
Yeah, he's a man. I blocked him about 10, 11 times now, but he keeps going.
Just tell him to stop. I mean, if you have any influence over him, can you tell him to stop?
Because he's calling me, calling me pedophile and all kinds of things.
So, I mean, he's calling, he is going in real life. He's calling my phone number.
You know what? I told you about Kitty. She was 20 years old and I always take care of them,
Vett and everything. And she, you know, the vet said it was her time and they had to put
And Crystal, oh, you killed the cat Crystal, you killed Milo you didn't you let him suffer in your closet going live every day on IG and people told her take care Milo because he loves you.
He used to hug her when she'd get all crazy on her lives.
And she didn't care.
And she ignored it. And then all of a sudden Milo was gone and she didn't even go to take him to the vet. She sent her dad to take him to my to take Milo to the vet to put to sleep.
Oh my God. She doesn't want them anymore. And then she got another young cat and she had that cat declawed.
Yeah, I know. And that's not what you're supposed to do. That's awful. You know, just learn to trim their claws or just don't have any pets if you're more worried about your furniture.
And that was another thing. I was sending her furniture that Vernon stole from her.
Gia was the one that got involved and she went on the panel or
Karen's not going to give you that crystal.
You need to grow up and get your shit together.
Yeah, there was a lot of shit and she celebrated Gia's death.
The truth about Gia is in the end,
she was unhappy with the guy that she was with and then also her sister's husband
would mess with her because he was in discord and he'd catch her in there and tell her family.
So they had an argument with the family because he was yelling and the sisters said, look, you need to, you know, they didn't want her doing what the escort whatever she was doing.
So anyway, she decided to leave that guy.
And she told me that she was moving in with the guy that she used to date years ago and he was way older. And he's the one that got her in the porn.
So that didn't work out and then she they were doing drugs and it was fentanyl in it and she she never woke up
Always hanging up on me
Okay, whoever it is. It is the same person sham same person's calling me over and over again
Okay, I mean, it's like I mean it's like you're saying it's not him. I mean, it's like he's using all I mean
It's the same guy. He had a different voice than Tony. I know he's now he's calling from Texas number from Texas that blade
I know blade
Who are you?
He keeps hanging up on me. Hello. That's weird man. He doesn't have anything to do. Just blowing you up like that
He lives alone. You know, he's on like the 50th ever. Let's come back piece of shit
Well, that's what you are big tall sexy Rob. You fucking ugly fat disgusting
I like Samoan people, but you're a you're disgracing the Samoan Samoan race, okay?
You're a disgrace to it. Samoans would eat you for a barbecue. They make a luau pig out of you
You fucking motherfucker. Stop calling me
Well, now he's going to keep on because just because of your reaction.
Damn.
Yeah.
You got to be careful with me.
Look at the text message I'm getting.
It says 50 year old bum.
That's what Brandon says.
Brandon says bum.
Get a job bum.
Ha.
Flag.
Methodics.
Are you sure that's not Brandon?
Because that's what he was doing.
Remember last week?
Yeah.
Bum.
Because when we saw that, remember that video where he calls those girls bums?
Where he said oh here. Oh, so that's him and that's weird because he stalks me when I get on your panel. He knows
Yeah, yeah, but hey, you know that lady know that looks scared and she said that she
Had a bad experience with Brandon and she dated him and she said he took advantage of me
But she sounded a little slow whatever and she wanted my YouTube and she was sending me her link
I don't know her. I mean if she wants to talk to somebody about it
Maybe you if she wants to tell her story about her bad experience with Brandon that he took advantage of her
She said I don't know her
So and then she left when she put her link in the back. I mean it must have been bad, but
Leave beta alone. Look at this. You see that for
For what does it say for too long leave her the fuck alone sicko leave her alone bitch?
You're so short short and frail and old
To be part of the document your whole family tree you love that pedophile Brandon Brandon's your pedophile friend
And then he keeps posting these pictures of many Manson putting a razor blade to his vagina
Yeah, oh you just say Brandon was in crystals chat they said and she's the one calling him a petto
I mean, she's in a fight with gamble and then she's saying, you know
That's why she got mad at me because she said I was talking to petto and he's all in his chat
Like he thinks that she's gonna, you know be cool with him
It's like she knows better because he's psycho using that old pig. That's why I was done with him
It's like if you were my friend
Why would you even have that old fat pic of me from 2016 saying
Rg saying that you're 350 pounds. You're not I saw
Look at what you look like if you want to get his podcast information. He was doxxed. He saw me
asshole
A lot of people see me and that was 2016 asshole people change
I saw I saw inx on camera. She looks like lies the monelly. I mean, it's like really like, you know, you know
But you're, but you're, but you're like a little petite thing. It's like, you know, you are, I mean, I don't know, now they're calling me short and stuff like that. I have AIDS, Rob. Okay, really. So Shan, this is your friend, calling it, saying I have AIDS coming on.
I have wavy hair though, and I hate wavy hair.
Yeah, well, you look really good and it's like so I have no makeup either. I don't even need makeup, you know
And I certainly don't look my age
You don't you don't you don't you know at all. Yeah, people freak out sometimes even my doctor
Oh, well, you're like, you know, basically like almost like a 90 year old woman in like a
I'm not that old God and my dad looked like he was 60 when he was 83 when he passed away
Hey, I know right American like me and that's I wish I didn't wasn't born in the state
So my sister and younger youngest brother were born overseas, so they get dual citizen ships
Me and my other brother stuck with American citizenship because I want to get out into states
I'm not trying to blame you shan
I'm just saying the person you're defending right there is
Texting me as we speak saying all these things to me and then coming on all these alts and it's like
Okay, this is the guy you know,
then use your influence on him if you have any.
I mean, I'm with this person,
but either he's pretending to be somebody else,
or, but it's like,
because I did talk to this person on the phone,
and he was saying horrible, horrible, disgusting things to me,
threatening my family,
and calling me, saying I have AIDS,
and all the same shit, right?
I'm not blaming you, Shan.
I'm just saying, like, I'm still getting these messages.
Listen, you hear it over and over again.
I'm just getting messages, messages, messages, right?
Maybe it's RG calling you.
I bet it's him.
Probably it didn't sound like RG on the phone. See, but I'm just I'm essentially you know, champ
There's somebody that you think maybe you know, they're using your your friends name or yeah
He's going real life. It's real life is calling my cell phone. You hear it. You're over and over
Yeah
Over it's the same person. Okay. How do you get my phone number, right?
Beta gives it out apparently, right? Oh, she gave it out. Oh, I thought you gave it to us. So she did your information
Yeah, she gave my address and my phone number to Eldo. Yeah, he proved it. Yeah, he showed it
Yeah, I have the text right here where he um, she shared my
My Zell information right here
Everything then
Here here. There you go. Oh, I'll take this off. Yeah, he's still going
Yeah
Yeah, that's there's my phone number and this is beat us that sharing this and she and she she said oh
Yeah, that's her sharing it. I just see message with the psyche awakens
See right here. This is her
Princess be that's her. Oh my god. Are you serious? So she's the one doxing people. She says her
Ex-brand doxed her birth certificate. That's not true. She gave it to Q. He said it again
That she doxed it to him. She was drunk
Guys you're such a liar man. She lies so much
Listen to this guys. You're you testing me. Yeah, that's texting
That's what Brandon was doing a few days ago. I blocked him everywhere
Right, and he talks as he watches us and he's sitting there. You know just weird. It's like he needs to get a life
Right. I mean he doesn't have a pool or office or anything. He's the one living in a dump
I've never lived in a dump. I come from a family with a lot of money
My mom especially her dad was a politician in South America and so was her
Fiancée before she took off and married an American and
That came to the states to have me shit. She should have stayed there. I wish I was born there
I really want to leave the states I didn't plan on staying here forever
It's like I'm my two younger siblings have dual the citizenship
Probably leave beat it alone fag it says okay, then it says welcome to Kiwi Farms, and I GG er
Then he does all the Jewish stars then he says
Stop mentioning beta or else son of the my mom's name. You're texting yourself for attention
Mentioned beta again, and it's over. You see the Jewish stars. He's making it. Stop. Stop mentioning beta. Stop mentioning beta
Guys, I'm not doing this real time. This is like actually really happening. Okay, Sam
This is what the person is sending me turning my mom threatening myself
What number is he using? You know, they do track it when you go to the police because my number was tracked
when I was using this fake number, so in 2020, 2022 actually.
Guys, call 346-766-7182, okay?
Yeah, but still, when the police say they do track it, you know, because that's how they found me.
Somebody complained, especially when you get these type of calls, they'll track it for you. You do a police report.
This is psycho. Also, there's an app to put on your phone and it's it helps you find the fake numbers
It's you pay pay for it though, but it works to have fat cow Karen Lattimer to take her old fucking whale ass to bed
Lose weight. Shut up loser fat ass
You wish I was fat dumbass
That's a complete loser who doesn't have anything. I mean he's up all night
Blowing you up. No life. No woman. It says you're the one harassing me old-ass bitch
Who's cool? Who's that? Oh, that's Brandon raw. It says big tall sexy Rob, you know big tall sexy Rob
He's doing all the right Brandon, but you said it's somebody else, you know
Well, I know I know who big tall sexy Rob is but there's there's text me over and be beta was fat
You want to see her pictures? I mean shit cuz she was fat and they're and they have those pictures of her and that wasn't
Ten years ago like me. That's recent a few years ago
Yeah, just ignore me. He's a piece of shit. He's a mistake. Oh, yeah, it takes me the number. I'll find it for you
It's not be blown up with the screaming of lambs
It'll stay on 12 hours and when they hang up boom it keeps ringing them back. It doesn't stop
Let's give it to you on air three four and when you get their number you can spoof them and call them with their own number
I'm gonna send it to you right now. I'm sending you the number
to me in the text. Yes, I'll do it. I'll take care of that because they'll get a million
calls. Yep, I'm getting a lot reported for doc saying I'm getting, oh, I didn't delete
this stream anyway. Yeah, my sister's ex is the cop so they could find it. Thank you.
Well, there's a number there. I sent it to you. There you go. Okay, cool. That's an idiot, fat,
so it doesn't have a live calling you all night long. Yeah. He doesn't get off the computer.
Nope, he doesn't. He's obsessed. And this is the same person that's been harassing me before. So, um, yeah, be
Beed up most of Bobby. That's it's beat a b i t a. So I'll dox her and I got her information
She's stupid because she highlighted somebody doxing her the new address
right
Right piece of shit. She's a liar and she just uses people you would if I show you what she sent me on Alex
Telling me to go to the court with that information
Because she got information from Amber
Yeah, she's a liar
I've got so much on her and then Astrid had sent me the horrible recording
She left her threatening her kid and all of that and she was begging us and I get rid of her
I don't know how to get rid of her, but she goes back and forth with her
Right, you know, I'm just sick of these people, but yeah, I'll do something with that number.
Thank you so much. I mean, I can do it on the computer too. And that way the calls, it just rings, rings, rings.
But yeah, what an asshole, but B doesn't want to send him probably, but if it's Brandon Quintana, he's fucked.
I know. Well, I want to show, I want to show this clip of what you had a brand in where he was talking to these. They look like they're 14 or 15 year old girls.
This is very real.
Yeah.
And then
Somebody else called, oh, Crystal was even calling him a pedo and he's over there trying to be in her chat. She's the one that can't stand on the most.
And that's why she got furious at me talking to him. She goes, why are people talking to that pedo?
He grows and she didn't even notice him in the chat, but she hates him the most.
She said yeah that pedo because somebody said that he was in her chat and she goes
Oh, he's a pedo and he's over there trying to kiss her ass like he thinks she's gonna pay attention to him
I know I know it's a sad. They hate him. Everybody does KK
K barry all of them blocked me because of him and Barry was even
Saying that they how led it his chats. He said she's she's talking to a fucking pedo, you know, we were cool
So I'm gonna reach out to them, you know, I feel bad because they're better people. They don't do the shit he does
But I never give them no chance. Here we go Karen. I'm gonna show it real quick. Here we go
This is the brand in Quintana
Talking to miners on the monkey app and inventing that is a pedophile. Here we go
You got to talk to noelle because she said she she raped her
She said he she took advantage and she was almost crying
Oh, I have his parent's name. I found a parent
I have a screenshot
Thank you, yeah
like me.
What a weirdo to be on the app for kids, like is he stalking those kids there and he lies
about vegan, oh yeah, if she was my girlfriend, no, she said that's crazy, you know, she's,
he was creepy.
Yeah, well he says Bob some few donate five dollar donations. That's all he could afford
Yeah, like anyone saying Brandon send me a lot of money send me two to five dollar donations
But and so, you know, it's like, you know, wow, I mean, it's like, I mean, I mean even I mean
sending donations does not negate
Doxing my entire family harassing me and stuff like that. I mean, I mean you can't people are trying to like say, oh
I mean, he's doxxed and donated.
Well, you have to see what they're doing to me.
I mean, it's like, I mean, it's just sort of.
He was like practically demanding money from me because you gave him a hundred dollars still going on about the hundred dollars that
When I said don't get him on and and he said he was he'd pay a hundred dollars
And I said I'll match it and then he left but there was no hundred dollars given to you
$100 given you know, it's like you know, he was still going on about it all week. Will you give him a hundred dollars?
He said it. He said it. He didn't say it. I said, you know, he's just crazy. I've never met anybody crazy like that. He's unhinged
I don't, I don't like him, he's a piece of shit.
But yeah, so I'm sorry, but I found his parents, you know?
I don't give a fuck, and he's fucking with me.
I'm glad I never gave him my number.
And I found his real number too, 505.
There you go, look at me, more calls.
George Wallace says I'm a bunch of rejects.
Well, George Wallace, you're a reject, George Wallace,
because you're not even allowed in this chat.
Get out of here, you n-word.
Bye.
I mean, George Wallace, I mean, who gives a fuck?
Who even cares?
George Wallace, you're just a lame.
I mean, so many people are just so lame, INX.
They're just so lame.
They're just so sad.
I mean, they're sitting,
do I ever sit in anybody's chat and go?
Yeah, come here.
Yeah, go ahead.
He's chatting fucking harassing on the phone. Do I fucking send anything to read his house? Do I fucking know I just fight back
You know cuz I'm not afraid of these people
Everyone else is afraid. You know, I'm not afraid because I will go after you. Okay, you will be revealed these people
Look, I'm okay. Again. He's on a thousand and use that big rock big tall sexy Rob
They may be as big tall sexy Rob this whole time. Call me Cyra. I mean Brandon Quintana get lost
Get lost brand nasty look in with his tummy with his stomach hanging out and oh
Some and then he lied about my friend Nancy. She doesn't know who he is
She said he's gross-looking when she saw him
Comments, but you know, he was her number at because she she's didn't there's no way she wanted to talk to him
No, no, he has big tits. I mean he has he has a bigger tits. He's got tits. Yeah, he's not doesn't work out or anything
No, no
And he's like, oh, well, this is my new girlfriend.
He has a picture of an AI picture of him on the beach
with this woman with dyed hair, this romantic picture
of Hawaii.
An AI, right?
Yeah, he's crazy.
He's never been outside of this country.
He's full of shit.
Yeah, yeah, it's disgusting.
And he's like, oh, well, this is it.
Who's on that?
So RG's here.
What's it like on RG?
What, RG?
You're on the air, RG?
Yeah, hello. Hello. Hello. You're on the air with Lou. Hi. What's what's going on a division and I since I keep going
What do you have to say?
I know I just want to call INX a fat cow.
Shut up, you're a cow. Look at you, man.
You wish, Ms. Thang.
He's queer, man.
I was just looking at his profile over the podcast.
Watch what he's going to be interrupted on his shows.
Blast that information out.
But yeah, Kiwi, I think they're looking for him,
so I'm going to dox him.
I didn't dox him.
I was doing something else there.
And so yeah, but I saw that about him that they they're looking for him or whatever
Yeah, yeah, he's gay. He's got he's got a gay boyfriend. He is gay
He's gay that's what they said it and Kiwi. Yeah, he's gay. Oh my gosh on all the time
He's all on the time. He's he's got a fat little boyfriend
And he's dude. That's a podcast wait till we call in over here
Ruin him
Steve Pokemon podcast please go ahead and do that you're more than welcome
Here's my coin clapping
Yeah, he's a thing. Yeah, he's gay and yeah, it's Michael. That's his boyfriend's name Michael
My god Michael Steven and Michael. Oh my god, Steven. Hey, yeah, and they have a little
Pickles is our baby, right? They're gonna be his pickles. We've been clapped RG. I'm sorry
What is a dog's name and it's
It's pickles pickles pickles. Okay. I didn't know the dog's name. Yeah, he's gay
He's on 24 seven all the time and and you know, it's like no life. Where's his gay man? His gay gay wife
I think he talks a female role
Oh, here we go. I mean
Hello, hello, who's that? Hello, you're on the air you hung up
Hung up Steve grow up Steve holder. He looks old as shit too, man. What do I hold it see 59 60
60 years old. Hey Karen doesn't hate gays because you know, I'm gay. I've never been gay. I was married dumbass
They say you hate gays and I she doesn't know. No, I don't hate gays. I just hate him her
Gay fakes and when they fake their like they're straight. That's what I hate
My mom had a friend he was her hair stylist and and he was gay
Yeah, my mom too. My mom too had a friend and she was telling me she's like what a hair stylist
I was gay. He I think he passed away from AIDS or something like that
But you know he did too. That was the first time I heard of AIDS. He passed away. Yeah
But you know what I don't have HIV or AIDS I'm almost celibate, you know, it's like I really have
I probably had had sex the amount of times you can count on two hands, you know
I mean in my life, you know, I'm I talk a big game and I flirt with people
But I'm really like, you know, not Alex does not have gay
She's not doesn't have AIDS or any of that though, you know, and I've repeated something. I was mad at her, but that's awful to say
It is helpful to say, I don't have her blood test.
I don't know what's going on with her,
but she's actually going after me too,
saying that I'm harassing her when she is giving me
death threats, OK?
You want to see my?
That's what Crystal's saying.
Where's the proof?
She was harassing me from all these group chats and discord.
And I showed the proof.
I have proof on my.
channel all the videos the call log have heard not leaving me alone and
You know, there's this fat cunt named sweepy that's that's unbeat is like, you know doxing team
So this fat cunt sweepy actually I have a real picture
I'll put up I'll put a real picture up because sweepy, you know, you are 300 pounds and we know it for sure
We know you're 300 pounds you fat disgusting twat
Okay, you're disgusting you're a baby witch you think you're a fucking real witch
You are a baby witch.
You're disgusting.
I don't care how dirty my thumbnail is.
It's not as dirty as your fucking heart and your soul.
Oh, I'm triggered.
Sweepie, you're a fucking fat cunt.
You're a cow.
You're a literal cow.
Show your real picture of besides squeaky.
Oh, I know for sure.
Yeah.
Okay, let's talk Sweepie.
I look at like a bra.
No, don't talk, sir.
Don't talk, sir.
I shouldn't, but she's saying I'm disgusting
and triggered and stuff like that.
I shouldn't talk, sir?
No, don't dox her. No, I'm gonna I'm glad to Karen Karen tell me not to again. I won't but I'm a sick bum
No, that's gone too far. You know, she doesn't want to show herself then you got to respect that some people don't want to
Because there's a lot of crazy trolls online
100 pounds on YouTube on YouTube 700 pounds. I shouldn't show her she was on my 600 pound life
I can show a clip of her from my 600 pound life. Let me show it. Hold on. You know, she was on that show my 600 pound life
You heard that show he was on the show or you're just so yeah, yeah, I'm gonna show and they're washer on the patent the porch
Like her boyfriend actually has to hose her down on the porch. Okay, you're ready to see her
I mean, this is I mean, it's so disgusting. I'm so sorry, but yeah, I have sweet peas
I have her on my 600 pound life
Yeah, here she is right here. I got her right here. Here she is. I got her right here here
Once I get you guys
Let's hear
Are you sure it's her or it's her once again. Here she is. Oh my gosh. She just fell or that's somebody on the show
Oh, no, it's her. This week. This week. He right here the real sweepy. Oh my god
That's really her or is that somebody?
He was on a reality show
i'm in so much pain right now i don't think i can get up and i don't know what i'm gonna do
she's like beat it ban me sweebie she's like beat it bans me and i can't just i can't even myself
right sweebie there's fair bitch all right this is her
that's that's Lucy on the name yeah
i just don't want your leg to get me worse you should get hurt her leg you heard it
I just need a moment and I wish my mom would leave me alone if I just take a
second I can see if I can get up because I don't want to have to call an
ambulance or any help I just want to get in my room and eat and put this
behind me I gotta go I gotta go guys I have emergency I'll be back okay you're
gonna end it